[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":1175,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":3774,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure that  when we  combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":1056,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":4832,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5030,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":9865,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":986,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":10855,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2400,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":13256,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":669,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":13926,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4152,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":18079,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":823,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":18904,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":1954,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":20859,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 =  2 and 2  is less than 6.","rt":764,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":21624,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2337,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":23961,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":868,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":24831,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and the n add th e second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2199,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":27031,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":721,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":27754,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1978,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":29735,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":783,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":30519,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2454,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":32974,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":729,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":33705,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3289,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":36994,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":864,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":37859,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3184,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":41044,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":824,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":41870,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":1064,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":42938,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"N ow that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":119033,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":161972,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":9192,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":171165,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Corr ect! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1594,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":172761,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2680,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":175443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":840,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":176284,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /> <br /> ( Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":1896,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":178181,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":813,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":178996,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2047,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":181045,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":775,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":181822,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2131,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":183954,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":7304,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":191260,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is  also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":48525,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":239786,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator unde r +<sub> 6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":589927,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":829714,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":7910,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":837631,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1385,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":839017,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator unde r +<sub> 6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2221,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":841239,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":8536,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":849777,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a ge nerator  is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2503,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":852282,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1688,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":853972,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3535,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":857508,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1064,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":858573,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":20397,"trial_type":"in structio ns","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":878971,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":9952,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":888924,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":5415,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":894341,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3392,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":897734,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":" 2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3864,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":901599,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4899,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":906499,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2899,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":909400,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4333,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":913734,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12 -0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. Four plus one equals five which is lower than nine so no subtraction is necessary. ","response_history":["5. Four plus one equals five which is lower than nine so no subtraction is necessary. "],"rt":28991,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":942726,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. 8 plus 4 = 12 - 9 = 3","response_history":["3. 8 plus 4 + ","3. 8 plus 4 +","3. 8 plus 4 = 12 - 9 = 3"],"rt":20587,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":963314,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got  your ans wer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"1. I think 1 was an identifier but I don't recall why or how. ","response_history":["1. I think 1 was an identifier but I don't recall why or wh","1. I think 1 was an identifier but I don't recall why or w","1. I think 1 was an identifier but I don't recall why or how. "],"rt":48417,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1011732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4047226,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":5058959,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2841,"trial_type":"question ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":5061801,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2777,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":5064579,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6. nince minus 3 + 6 ","response_history":["6. nince minus 3 + 6 "],"rt":20702,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":5085283,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No? I don't understand the generators  exactly . I think it's... 0 and 8? So then 2 would not be?","response_history":["Yes? I don't understand the generators exactly. I think it's... 2 ","Yes? I don't understand the generators exactly. I think it's... 2","Yes? I don't understand the generators exactly. I think it's... ","N? I don't understand the generators exactly. I think it's... ","No? I don't understand the generators exactly. I think it's... 0 and 9? ","No? I don't understand the generators exactly. I think it's... 0 and 9?","No? I don't understand the generators exactly. I think it's... 0 and 9","No? I don't understand the generators exactly. I think it's... 0 and 8? So then 2 would not be?"],"rt":64679,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":5149964,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. I don't think  so, but  am not sure. ","response_history":["No. I don't think so, but i'","No. I don't think so, but i","No. I don't think so, but am not sure. "],"rt":13859,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":5163824,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. I don't think it is, I didn't understand generators","response_history":["No. I don't think it is, I didi","No. I don't think it is, I didn't understand generators"],"rt":13010,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":5176836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. I don't understand. ","response_history":["No. I don't  understa nd. "],"rt":8745,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":5185582,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":11430,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":5197013,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 +n 0 = ","response_history":["1 +n 0 = "],"rt":38894,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":5235908,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inv erse of  an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x +n 3 = n-3=inverse","response_history":["It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as I had to take a 5 min break ","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as I h","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as I ","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as I","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me. I think it might be.. ","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me. I t","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me. I ","It would be nice if I could go back and  look at  the instructions as the inverse confused me. I","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me. You get the un","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me. You get the u","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me. You get the inverse ","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me. You","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me. Yo","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me. Y","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x plus ","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x plus","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the invers e confus ed me.  Maybe it's,  x plu","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x pl","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x p","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x +n 10 =  x - ","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x +n 10 =  x -","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x +n 10 =  x ","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x +n 10 =  x","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x +n 10 =  ","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x +n 10 = ","It wou ld be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x +n 10 =","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x +n 10 ","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x +n 10","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x +n 1","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x +n 3","It would be nice if I could go back and look at the instructions as the inverse confused me.  Maybe it's,  x +n 3 = n-3=inverse"],"rt":132337,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":5368248,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing  whether  it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I can't recall how to know this. Re-reading the instructions would be nice. ","response_history":["I can't recall how to know this. Re-reading the instructions would be nice. "],"rt":29504,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":5397753,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5285,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":5403039,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4808,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":5407849,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":12669,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":5420520,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"No, because if 1 +6 4 = 5 then x is not a multiple or divisor of n","response_history":["No, becaue ","No, becaue","No, because if 1 +6 2 = 3 then ","No, because if 1 +6  = 3  then "," No, because if 1 +6 4 = 3 then ","No, because if 1 +6 4 =  then ","No, because if 1 +6 4 = 5 then neither ","No, because if 1 +6 4 = 5 then neither","No, because if 1 +6 4 = 5 then neithe","No, because if 1 +6 4 = 5 then neith","No, because if 1 +6 4 = 5 then neit","No, because if 1 +6 4 = 5 then nei","No, because if 1 +6 4 = 5 then ne","No, because if 1 +6 4 = 5 then n","No, because if 1 +6 4 = 5 then x is not a multiple or divo","No, because if 1 +6 4 = 5 then x is not a multiple or divisor of n"],"rt":76847,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":5497369,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":11080,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":5508452,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I think only sometimes depending on the value of x","response_history":["I think only sometimes depending on which ","I think only sometimes depending on which","I think only sometimes depending on whic","I think only sometimes depending on whi","I think only sometimes depending on wh","I think only sometimes depending on w","I think only sometimes depending on the value of x"],"rt":31618,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":5540071,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub>  always,  sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":14099,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":5554171,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2713,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":5556886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"28","response_history":["28"],"rt":2179,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":5559066,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college , no deg ree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":3845,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":5562913,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Algebra 1","response_history":["Algebra 1"],"rt":8471,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":5571386,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 -  used it  but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3971,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":5575358,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":4167,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":5579526,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - n ot at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3549,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":5583076,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3322,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":5586399,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2218,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":5588618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What  is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1933,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":5590552,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":3857,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":5594410,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3563,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":5597974,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments o n this H IT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Thank you for the opportunity, I wish the best for your research :)","response_history":["Thank you for the opportunity, I wish the best for your research :)"],"rt":11346,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":5609321,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]